hkcl.in 2019-06-05

# HKCL - Privacy Policy

**A. GENERAL**

This privacy policy governs your use of the HSSC NIYUKTI mobile application that is hosted at Haryana Knowledge Corporation Ltd. (HKCL)’s e-Gov Mobile App Account in Google Play Store. Haryana Staff Selection Commission is committed to the protection of personal information provided by the users to us. You agree that your use of Haryana Staff Selection Commission’s web platform implies your consent to the collection and use of your personal information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. This information provided through these applications may not have any legal sanctity and are for general reference only, unless otherwise specified. However, every effort has been made to provide accurate and reliable information through these applications. Users are advised to verify the correctness of the facts published here from the concerned authorities. No user information is rented or sold to any third party. When a user uses the platform, HSSC may collect users’ mobile phone number, login information and other personal information for communication purposes with the user. A high standard of security is maintained by HSSC for its users; however the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. So, whilst we will do our best to protect user information, particularly with respect to protection of personal data, we cannot ensure the security of user data transmitted to us via the internet or any other medium. 

**B. User Provided Information**

HSSC NIYUKTI mobile application does not collect any user information, however, this app is directly linked to the HSSC’s recruitment portal and a user is able to view all the information published by HSSC on this app. The user information collected on web portal of HSSC can only be accessed by the user using his/her login credentials generated on web portal. The information you provided may be used to contact you from time to time to provide you with important information and required notices. 

**C. DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We may disclose User provided and Automatically Collected Information:   
• as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process;  
• when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;  
• with our trusted service providers who work on our behalf, do not have an independent use of the information we disclose to them, and have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this privacy statement. You can stop all collection of information by the Application easily by uninstalling the Application. You may use the standard uninstall processes as may be available as part of your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network.

**D. Misuse by Non Targeted Users**

All mobile apps are meant for use by the targeted audience only. Misuse by non-targeted users should be prevented by owner of the mobile. 

**E. Security**

We are concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We provide physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect information we process and maintain. 

**F. Your Consent**

By using the Application, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. 

**G. Contact us**

If you have any questions regarding privacy while using the Application, or have questions about our practices, please contact us via email at [ hryssc@gmail.com ](mailto:hryssc@gmail.com)
